Johnson Lee

Westfield, IN 46062 johnson.hwang1008@gmail.com +1 317 645 3194

Experienced Dishwasher with little over 4 years of experience in a fast-paced kitchen environment. Proficient at adapting to unexpected situations and making sure environmental operations run smoothly as much as possible by handling multiple task simultaneously. Seeks new opportunity in unfamiliar environments in other departments to grow self development.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Dishwasher and Prep Cook

Miracle Asian Modern Cuisine - Carmel, IN November 2016 to Present

Operated and maintained cleaning equipment and tools, including dishwasher, hand wash stations, potscrubbing station and trash compactor. • Helped team meet expected demands by restocking work areas throughout restaurant such as server stations and supply cupboards. • Stepped into additional roles during busy times to boost coverage of important stations/ • Efficiently loaded and unloaded dishwashers, preparing appetizers and cleaning desired dishes. • Boosted team efficiency by keeping kitchen areas organized, clean and properly sanitized. Completed extra cleaning work on garbage cans, racks, dry storage areas and other fixtures to keep kitchen spotless. Assisted with kitchen prep work to help operations run smoothly and meet customer needs. • Worked with chemicals such as detergent, rinse agents and sanitizers to protect customer health.

Wendy's Crew Member/Cashier

Wendy's - Westfield, IN May 2021 to November 2021

- · Communicated with vendors
- · Organized new hire orientations
- Welcomed all customers
- Took customer orders
- · Ran the cash register
- Responsible for answering the phone
- · Prepared orders and food items
- Cleared tables
- Opened and closed the restaurant
- Kept the store clean
- · Labeled boxes and containers
- Provided exceptional customer service
- Managed cash flow with drawer and vault
- Keeping up with a fast environment

Education

High school diploma

Westfield High School - Westfield, IN August 2016 to May 2020

Skills

- Food Preparation
- Cleaning Experience
- Kitchen Experience
- Meal Preparation
- Kitchen Management Experience
- Busser
- Food Safety
- Culinary Experience
- Restaurant Experience
- Inventory Control
- Serving Experience
- Customer service (2 years)
- Retail Sales

Languages

• English - Fluent